



### Specialties

- > UI/UX Design
- > Interaction Design
- > Project Management
- > Story Boarding
- > Style Boarding
- > Prototyping
- > Graphic Design
- > SVG Icons
- > Illustration
- > Typography

# Tools

- > Sketch
- > Adobe Creative Suite
- > Affinity Designer & Photo
- > NPM/ WebPack
- > HTML/CSS
- > SASS
- > Vue.js
- > Vue/Nuxt
- > Angular
- > Bootstrap

#### Profile

Art Director in the '90s in Miami. Mid-'90s moved to London, England and worked at top ten Advertising agency TBWA (Omnicom). In the late '90s I transitioned to 'Multimedia', UI design. Now it's all UI/UX.

Guru-level with all Adobe CS, Sketch. Axure wireframing, though often straight to Bootstrap design inbrowser. Love reducing complexity to simplicity, when designed well, the user interface seems inevitable.

## Experience

- > 1998 present Always Freelancing
- Tennessee Dept of Education Contract, Nashville, TN, 12/2016 – 06/2017
- > Civic Inc.

Contract, Nashville, TN, 09/2013 - 02/2015

> JPay.com

Full-time, Miami, FL, 2008 – 2013 Many projects, basically a one-man Web Dev department

- > JPay.com
- > Mobile App
- > Phablet App B2C
- > MLotto Project App & Website
- > Safari Ltd.

Contract, Miami, FL, 2007 - 2008

- > Planning Group Int. (now Sapient Nitro) Contract, Miami, FL, 2006
- > Diaz & Cooper Adv.

Full-time, Miami, FL, 2003 - 2006

> Art Director & Web Designer at TBWA Full-time, London UK, 1998 – 2000

### **Education**

- International Fine Arts College, 1987, Miami, FL, Commercial Art, AA Degree
- > Trent College, 1984, Long Eaton, UK

Boarding school in England, received Art Scholarship. Played Rugby for my county.

#### Referrals

- Don Pham
  Project Manager
  don.kim.pham@gmail
  (954) 801-9975
- Mike Mack Coder mikemack88@gmail.com (415) 509-1909
- Joanna Perry Creative Director joanna@nomadhome.net +44 788-418-7100